

KELVIN LEUNG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

A positive and self-motivated full-stack developer with 7+ years of work experience in many different front-end and back-end languages, responsive frameworks, database, mobile app development with Java for Android devices & Swift for iOS devices, and best code practices.

CONTACT

Address:

Brisbane, Australia

Email:

kelvinleung.aus@gmail.com

Website:

http://kelvinleung.me

LinkedIn:

https://linkedin.com/in/kelvinlwy

GitHub:

https://github.com/kelvinlwy

SKILLS

Mobile Development:

Android • iOS

Programming Languages:

JS • Java • Swift • Objective-C • PHP • SQL

Web Technologies:

Node.js • CSS3 • HTML5 • Jquery • ReactJs • React Native • AngularJs

Database:

MySQL • PostgreSQL • MongoDB

EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder & Tech Lead

2017 - Present

HAPPY DINOSAUR PTY LTD

Happy Dinosaur is an innovative advertising startup whose strategy is utilising spaces on takeaway coffee cup as medium and cafes as hubs to deliver clients' business message to target audiences in local communities.

My lead role is to design & develop both web & mobile platform for online system through performing requirements analysis, design, technology sourcing to implementation, maintenance, and product analysis; manage digital marketing and social media advertising.

Full Stack Web App Developer

Mar, 2017 - Sep, 2017

CHAPTECH

I am responsible for building a web platform written in modern software technologies. My responsibilities:

- Develop a complex web application from scratch for both frontend (with HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS) and backend (with Hapi.js, Node.js, MySQL)
- Implement GIS by using Mapbox API
- API design and development
- Testing, debugging, troubleshooting, maintainence, and application stability & performance improvement

Android Lead & Web Developer

May 2016 - Mar, 2017

IRECRUIT AUSTRALIA

I am responsible for the full lifecycle Android development through design, project architecture, implementation to debugging & troubleshooting, testing, and product release; the web application front-end development from project planning to translating UI design into code and handling & presenting business logic visually in the web interface.

Mobile App Developer

Jun 2011 - Apr, 2016

LOCATRIX COMMUNICATIONS

- Professional Android development with Java & iOS development with Swift
- Involved in full lifecycle for both enterprise internal & commercial mobile app development from scratch to

Customer Service Coordinator

VANTEC WORLD TRANSPORT(HK) LTD

Air Export Ops Officer

UPS SUPPLY CHAIN SOLUTIONS

EDUCATION

Griffith University

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Engineering, Electronic & Computer Engineering with Class IIA Honours

REFERENCE

ALEKSANDAR SVETSKI

Former CEO, iRecruit Australia Phone: +61 417 165 003

MARK WHITE

CEO, Locatrix Communications
Phone: +61 438 900 880